Rey
Just more 10 days guys
we will be seperating off to various places
Mario to Delhi
Battu to Chennai
Bunny to Bihar
I'll be in Namma Bengaluru
Rey Ninja, you?
For my EAMCET rank, I'll only get in a dumbass college here
Wow!
Hell with this Engineering, Why are we in it?
All our golden days are over ra!
No Matter What!
We have to do SOMETHING Today!
I even bought alcohol just because you wanted to drink,
What else do you wanna do?
Ehh Not like this! Something Memorable ra..
One Last Time?
Let's Watch THOSE VIDEOS?
Hey, I'm not visible!
Repeat Repeat
Let's Watch THOSE VIDEOS?
Ehh Nah that's Daily Routine.
Next Next!
Rey give your Ex's number we'll do a prank call.. kikikiki-
I told you not bring up that matter a Hundred times!
She was just a phase of my-
NOT AGAIN PLEASE!
Let's go for a car ride?
Rey.. What say?
I'm in. You?
Who'll get the Car?
Rey, Shall we ask him?
Reyy Mario..
Your Dad...
Will he give his car..?
MY DAD!?
What? Are you scared?
Rey...
He's My Daddy..
You know about him na..?
You wait!
Now if we take your car out secretly without your dad knowing it
And if we SAFELY keep it in the same place by the morning
Will there be any problem?
I didn't get it..
But how?
Now the time is 11, An in an hour,
He'll drink and get high and will just sleep off
Then if we go and Snatch away the Keys,
And have fun the whole night,
And if we keep car and keys n their places by 6am
There won't be any problem, What say?
Okay then,
We have 1 more hour!
Drink as much as you want to
Then Later?
With our Energy,
Whole Hyderabad should get HIGH!
Where are these keys?
Rey rey! Over there...
Just go and snatch!
No no!
No please..
Shivadarshini Believe Yourself!
Shut up!
Daddy...?
How many fingers are these?
Ehh snatch it up!
Yaayyy I've taken it I've taken it!
(singing emotional father song with uttermost love)
What?
I'll drive the car!
Get off, You can't even drive a Bike!
I said I'll Drive it Right !?
How many gears does a scooty have?
one on the left.. two on the right.. one plus one..
huh?
bro!
wear your seatbelt!
eheheehehhhee, get lost!
as you wish.
Get Ready Boys!
It's gonna be a WILD Ride!
(singing a telugu item song)
now.. what if
my dad get's to know that we done this?
haha is this the matter?
what can he do?
He may hit you as you are his son
What can he do to us?
What what?
You think he'll spare you guys?
He's already PISSED OFF on him for spoiling my life!!
Ehh who cares about this guy?
wait, then you guys?
I said NO to triples that day! But you said Nothing will happen and police won't be there..
My Dad saw that Picture!!
What is this??
I don't know anything Daddy,
It's all these people who made me do it...
Oh is it?
yes- no - daddy..-
UNCLE!!
My own dad never hit me!
Who are you to hit me!!?
Okay you may leave then..
Thank you Uncle,
God is Great..
YOU IDIOT!
OH MY GOD!
Ehh It's Fine ra..
He's asleep anyway
If we keep the car in its place by morning as you said,
Everything is Good!
Honesty is best policy
(singing that telugu item song again)
Who put the phone under my Buttocks?
It's mine only take it out
Who the hell calls at this hour..?
This Airtel guy has no time sense fr!
Mario..
what?
Your-
Da-
ITS YOUR DAD!
(BURSTS IN SHOCK)
What Should I do now??
You talk to him
You Talk to him please!
Oreyy what's happening?
Why is he Driving the CAR!!???
Are you Mad!!!!
JOCKEY JOCKEY JOCKEY DO SOMETHING!
My Dad will screw me up If anything happens to the carr!!!!
Where did I land up?
Where Am I?
With all these colors,
It's the Black hole my Maths Sir told about!
Mario?
CAR! CAR! CAR! CAR!
GET DOWN GET DOWN!
WHAT? WHY? WHEN?
Ehh Get Down!
I feel sleepy lemme sleep for a while..
Huh? What on earth are you speaking?
You Idiot!
Jockey, It's gone!
its gone its gone
Lemme do something then,
I'll go too!
Shit shit I'm dead...
Who built a tree on the road?
Hey Sleeping beauty, Wake up!
What's this guy doing?
(a lame telugu joke)
Why the car kiss tree man?
What happened?
It's screwed up! See
Do something
Go!
Okay okay..,
Let me handle
Do you think Mother board got damaged?
yes yes roger that roger that
Rey Jockey I'm having vomiting sensation-
Don't make me slap you, Get lost over there!
Once move that wire..
Can't we do anything?
My Dad is calling me Again!!
Rey I'm scared, You only talk something please I can't-
Hello?
Daddy?
Why did you do this?
Reyy he knows about it, We're done!
Daddy, I didn't do it wantedly-
I've taken care of you since you were born till now and
you're leaving to another state without me to study son?
I'm really worried about how will you take care of yourselves there my lovely son..
You know how much your daddy loves you??
For your next birthday, I'm giving off my Alto Car as  gift to you, Take It My Lovely son!
Car for me?
Really daddy?
WOW!
Thanks you Daddy!
I Love You My Son I Love You I Love You......
Okay Daddy, Love you!
(with a chumma on imaginary forehead)
What A Mess my god..
Why are you Laughing?
Don't Laugh!
It's a serious matter!
It's 2AM now
We gotta return by 6AM
And all this now..
ALL BECAUSE OF YOU!
SHUT UP!
Who gives the phone to someone who's driving?
Hey! I somehow managed it no?
you unsophisticated illiterate screwdrivers..
Rey, atleast listen to me now!
I'll drive the car now.
Keep Calm and Trust Bunny-
Ehh Get Lost you Dumbass!
you piece of shit..
its all because of him
You guys always treat me like this!
You neither give me the car nor anything!
Useless Car, Useless Friendship!
F@CK OFF!
How dare they humiliate me..
I'll show what I am!
EE SAALA CUP NAMDE!
Jockey,
We must solve this somehow..
We can't even find a mechanic at this hour..
I think there's this one person guys
Hey
Left or Right?
Left!
YOU STUPID I SAID LEFT!
Chinthamani Repair Shop..
Bhaskar MBBS!?
MBBS?
Who's this crazy guy?
Who studied MBBS and put up a Mechanic shop?
After Engineering, ours is the same too!
Ehh Cu the Crap!
Jockey!
go call him
I should only take care of everything..
These fingerprint fellows!
Uncle!
he's not responding
Shout! Shout!
Uncle!
UNKOOL!
Aaaahhh!!!! Who the hell is that?
Crawl in!
Really?
Yes Crawl In!
Rey!
Is he there inside?
Yes he is...
What's the matter?
We met with an accident, Please help us, Please!
Do you know what time it is?
Please Help us! We're done if My Dad knows about this...
Ehh move aside
Pretty good damage..
Let's cash them!
2000..
1000..
It costs 4000!
We don't have money!
Please help us somehow...?
even my bottle is completed...
Rey rey take out that bottle!!
You guys are Sharp!
Excuse me?
How long will it take anna?
come back after 2 hours!
you be right here and make sure everything's okay
Rey
WHY ME AGAIN?
NOO...
(singing a cute telugu song from KOT movie)
huh?
brother
Who's in that photo there?
Chinthamani...
my sweethot..
If everything was right, She would be with me only brother..
Bro! then..
you also had a breakup?
that means..
you too...?
COME COME LET'S SIT AND TALK
LETS SHARE OUR SADNESS
Brother..
Can you tell me your story?
Once upon a time, It was a beautiful Night..
What a Tragic Night...
I got shit scared..
leave it
it somehow got solved right?
But this is what we would be missing right?
Doing crazy ass stuff?
One or two?
god knows how many things we have done together
right from stealing lollipops from Murthy anna's shop
and buying one to make him trust us
getting drunk caught in Bunny's home..
yet nothing has changed
we're drinking in this guy's house now
the funny thing is..
It takes place in my house but I'm the only one who doesn't drink, what a character!
Hey!
what are you watching?
I'm learning Car Driving!
when I went to her house to ask for marriage,
They turned me down saying that
they already have a Doctor in their house!
I've put up this shop as there as no mechanic in their family
How can she leave me like that for this!!?
I put this name with deep love for her brother..
CHINTHAMANI REPAIR SHOP
She could see this shop only but,
couldn't she see my love behind this?
In another 10 days,
this fun,
and these memories,
will everything be over?
new place, and new people
can we adapt?
We all are very close since childhood
like it takes just 5 minutes to meet whenever we want to..
now we're going afar..
how then?
We'll stick together, right?
hey!
why are you getting emotional now?
Now we meet once every week..
later,
we might meet once every year..
Just because of that, you think we'll get seperated?
see guys!
I also like to spend time with you guys and relax
But career is also equally important right guys?
now if we work hard for these 4 years and get a good job,
life is set!
What say?
NOT AGAIN!!!
(singing emotional father sentiment song with love)
where's this guy?
I'm in a mess again..
what shall we do now?
in this moment,
We should only do something now!
Hold whatever you find near you!
No time for jokes guys!
serious.
Thank God, Finally we are home!
In English, this is called SpiderMan-Homecoming
Time is not 6 yet right?
there's another minute left
Ahh it's fine then
Okay but where is this Bunny?
mmm? bunnyyy...?
Bunnyy...?
NAMASTE GANG!!
Welcome to Rakesh Master Drywing Skool!
What we are gonna do now is, We'll learn how to drive
It's not at all a big deal, as easy as cooking an omlette
here you'll have a handbrake
you should lift it like JAAAIII
here you'll have gear
you should just push it forward like this
here you'll have an accelerator
you should just push it forward,
your car will start RACING OFF!
REEYYY HOW DO I STOP THIS?
BUNNY BUNNY THERE'S A WALL SLOW DOWN SLOW DOWN BUNNY!!!!
WALL WALL BUNNYYY!!!!